MICHAEL DELCORE

MichaelDelcore.com

Telephone: +1-619-601-2293 Location: Amsterdam

Email: nmdelcore@gmail.com Date of Birth: 15 February 1982

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/michaeldelcore Nationality: America; Holder of Dutch residence and work permit

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Front-End Web Developer professional with over 4 years of international experience. I have a diverse set of technical skills, problem-solving mindset, strong sense for aesthetics and integration. Successful in coordinating web projects from initiation to completion.

Skills: Ability to work as a team player as well as work independently; Proven coordination and administration skills; IT trainer; Cross-cultural experience.

Technical Skills: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, Bootstrap, jQuery, Ajax, Salesforce Commerce Cloud, VS Code, Jira, and Confluence.

Language Skills: English – native; Spanish – intermediate; Dutch – beginner

Qualities: A goal-driven, self-motivated, problem-solver with a strong commitment to delivering excellence.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

University of Denver

Denver, Colorado

Salesforce

San Francisco, California

Full-Stack Web Developer Certification

January 2018

B2C Commerce Developer Course with SFRA (CCD102)

February 2021

Developer for Salesforce B2C Commerce Course (CCD101)

November 2019

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Tillys

Tillys.com

April 2019 - September 2021

Salesforce Commerce Cloud Front-End Developer

- Lead administrator for all Realms, Control Center, Sandboxes, and Account Manager
- Code and data release manager
- Deliver solutions such as: curbside-pickup, same day delivery, and SFRA implementation

Gallery Furniture

GalleryFurniture.com

April 2018 - April 2019

Salesforce Commerce Cloud Front-End Developer

- Implement JavaScript controllers to add business logic
- Create reusable code, content slots/assets and promo & marketing campaigns
- Manage site data such as catalogs, product pages, and price books

Vaqara

Vagara.com

May 2009 – June 2013

Operations/Business Development Manager

- Managed accounting, staff, vendors, outsourcing, and new business development
- Revamped accounts receivable process, automating 90% of monthly client billing; saving the company approximately \$41,000 per year in payroll expenses
- Implement and managed global marketing campaigns to increase company awareness and sales